<resources>
    <string name="app_name">DemoApplication</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Demo</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">demo@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_gallery">Gallery</string>
    <string name="menu_slideshow">Slideshow</string>
    <string name="menu_tools">Tools</string>
    <string name="menu_share">Share</string>
    <string name="menu_send">Send</string>
    <string name="image_description">Image Description</string>
    <string name="home_title">Explore Android Platform</string>
    <string name="android_platform_details_text">This swipe up animation is done using MotionLayout, Let us see some more awesome features.</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="demo_text">Demo App</string>
    <string name="android_ml_title_text">Image Classification using TensorFlow Lite on Android</string>
    <string name="android_ml_title">TensorFlow Lite for Flowers</string>
    <string name="tensor_flow_detail_text"><Data><![CDATA[TensorFlow Lite provides all the tools you need to convert and run TensorFlow models on mobile, embedded, and IoT devices.
    The following guide walks through each step of the developer workflow and provides links to further instructions.
<br/>
<br/>
<b>1. Choose a model</b>
<br/><br/>A TensorFlow model is a data structure that contains the logic and knowledge of a machine learning network trained to solve a particular problem. There are many ways to obtain a TensorFlow model,
from using pre-trained models to training your own.
To use a model with TensorFlow Lite, you must convert a full
TensorFlow model into the TensorFlow Lite format—you cannot create or train a model using TensorFlow Lite.
So you must start with a regular TensorFlow model, and then convert the model.
<br/>
<br/>
<b>2. Convert the model</b>
<br/><br/>
TensorFlow Lite is designed to execute models efficiently on mobile and other embedded devices with limited compute
and memory resources. Some of this efficiency comes from the use of a special format for storing models.
TensorFlow models must be converted into this format before they can be used by TensorFlow Lite.

Converting models reduces their file size and introduces optimizations
that do not affect accuracy. The TensorFlow Lite converter provides options that allow you to further reduce file size and increase speed of execution, with some trade-offs.
<br/>
<br/>
<b>3. Run inference with the model</b>
<br/><br/>
Inference is the process of running data through a model to obtain predictions. It requires a model, an interpreter, and input data.
TensorFlow Lite interpreter
The TensorFlow Lite interpreter is a library that takes a model file, executes the operations it defines on input data, and provides access to the output.
The interpreter works across multiple platforms and provides a simple API for running TensorFlow Lite models from Java, Swift, Objective-C, C++, and Python.
<br/>
<br/>
<b>4. Optimize your model</b>
<br/>
<br/>
TensorFlow Lite provides tools to optimize the size and performance of your models, often with minimal impact on accuracy. Optimized models may require slightly more complex training, conversion, or integration.
<br/>
Machine learning optimization is an evolving field, and TensorFlow Lite\'s Model Optimization Toolkit is continually growing as new techniques are developed.
<br/><br/>
]]></Data>
    </string>
    <string name="explore_text">Click Explore to Recognize flowers.</string>
    <string name="coming_soon">Coming Soon !!!</string>
    <string name="coming_soon_detailed_message">Sorry, I still have to add the code for recognizing flowers using TensorFlow Lite on the Android platform.</string>
    <string name="okay">Ok</string>
</resources>
